{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/1006","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1006","name":"John Nichols Elementary","address":"3020 Burns","zipcode":"48214","owner":"Detroit Public Schools Communi","licenseNumber":"035057","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Public School","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-82.99826,42.36705","geojson":{"id":"1006","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-82.998261749,42.367048447]},"properties":{"name":"John Nichols Elementary","owner":"Detroit Public Schools Communi","address":"3020 Burns","zipcode":"48214","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"035057","establishmentid":"1006","establishment_type":"Public School","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"2021-06-08"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51623481","name":"Slows to Go Food Truck","address":"2940 Iroquois","zipcode":"48214"},{"establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","address":"8405 Mack Ave.","zipcode":"48214"},{"establishmentid":"4734","name":"Dot & Etta's Shrimp Hut Restaurant ","address":"9100 Mack Ave.","zipcode":"48214"},{"establishmentid":"433","name":"Dot and Etta's Shrimp Hut","address":"9100 Mack","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"1600","name":"Cornerstone School","address":"2411 Iroquois","zipcode":"48214"},{"establishmentid":"51622619","name":"Detroit Prep","address":"2411 Iroquois","zipcode":"48214"},{"establishmentid":"5284","name":"Conventional Missionary Baptist Church","address":"2255  Seminole","zipcode":"48214"},{"establishmentid":"316","name":"Cesar Chavez Academy Elementary","address":"8126 Vernor St.W.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"3803","name":"Diamondstar Pizza","address":"7927 Charlesvoix","zipcode":"48214"},{"establishmentid":"51623075","name":"Detroit Prep","address":"8411 Sylvester","zipcode":"48214"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"60759","inspectionDate":"2022-11-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"59722","inspectionDate":"2022-04-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"CAFETERIA","subLocation":"At the Equipment","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"56280","inspectionDate":"2021-10-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.19","violationDescription":"The temperature of the wash solution in manual WAREWASHING EQUIPMENT shall be maintained at not less than 110 F or the temperature specified on the cleaning agent manufacturer's label instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Manual warewash wash solution","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 110 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the First Compartment","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Change water frequently to maintain at least 110 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"CAFETERIA","subLocation":"At the Thermometer(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"CAFETERIA","subLocation":"At the Cooler (milk)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"54427","inspectionDate":"2021-03-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"53247","inspectionDate":"2020-10-29T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"Floor(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"At the Floor","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"seals","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"DINING AREA","subLocation":"At the Cooler (milk)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."}]},{"inspectionid":"49770","inspectionDate":"2019-11-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.114","violationDescription":"The PREMISES shall be free of items that are unnecessary to the operation or maintenance of the establishment such as EQUIPMENT that is nonfunctional, no longer used and free of litter.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Litter/debris","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not removed from facility","subProblem":"","location":"CAFETERIA","subLocation":"At the Debris","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove from facility/premises."}]},{"inspectionid":"48029","inspectionDate":"2019-06-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"44522","inspectionDate":"2018-12-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"Inside the Freezer(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"42511","inspectionDate":"2018-06-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Cooler (3 door)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."}]},{"inspectionid":"40768","inspectionDate":"2017-11-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"Inside the Walk-in freezer","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"38778","inspectionDate":"2017-05-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"Inside the Freezer(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\n\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"refrigeration","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Inside the Cooler (3 door)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-05-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."}]},{"inspectionid":"37140","inspectionDate":"2016-11-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"Floor(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Broken","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Floor tiles","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Hot holding unit","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1006"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}